<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Avanti</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 16:27:11 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 16:27:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cream Cheese Frosting Recipe</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/CakePicture.JPG&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:400px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph-center&quot;&gt; This is a cake my sister and I baked for Fourth of July, featuring, of course, this amazing frosting recipe. &#39;Shout out to my sister, we relate, we get the same attention&#39; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt; 
&lt;b&gt;Servings: Enough to frost a 10x10 cake (or 1 dozen cupcakes)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

3 ounces unsalted butter, softened &lt;br /&gt;
8 ounces whipped cream cheese&lt;br /&gt;
1.5 cups confectioner&#39;s sugar&lt;br /&gt;
3 teaspoons vanilla extract&lt;br /&gt;
2 teaspoons milk&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Recipe: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This is a delicious recipe for a quick, and very easy, frosting that isn&#39;t super runny. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

To begin with, beat the softened butter and cream cheese together with an electric mixer, on medium speed. While beating the butter and cream cheese, slowly add the powdered sugar. Once you have added all the sugar, add the milk, and beat for another minute on high speed. Then, add the vanilla extract and stir the frosting just until the extract is blended. Enjoy!!!
&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/2016/08/10/cream-cheese-frosting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/2016/08/10/cream-cheese-frosting.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stranded</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/trainstation.JPG&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:400px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt; 
One of my most memorable memories of my trip to NYC was when my sister and I went to her friend&#39;s wedding in Connecticut. We took the subway to Grand Central Station, from where we then took a train to get to Connecticut. As you can see in the picture above, Grand Central is absolutely stunning. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/traintrack.JPG&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:500px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt; Just as we entered Connecticut, our train stopped abruptly, and we were forced to get off of the train and wait for an unspecified amount of time. After over an hour of waiting, we were told that the bridge our train needed to cross was experiencing mechanical issues. As a result, we were forced to find other forms of transportation to get to our destination, and since so many of us were stranded, Uber surge prices soared, and finding an available taxi was difficult. Literally stranded in the outskirts of Connecticut, my sister and I panicked. Luckily, however, some of our very close family friends live in Connecticut and were ultimately able to give us a ride to the venue. Driving through Connecticut actually turned out to be a pretty neat experience. Although we got to the hotel, which is also where the reception was, much later than expected because of the train, we still got to attend a majority of the reception (and catch the second half of the Warriors semifinals game). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/churchCT.JPG&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:500px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt; Above is a picture of a beautiful church right near the train station. We passed the church as we were driving away from the station with our family friend. To be honest, I was surprised how calm (relatively) we stayed throughout the entire situation - part of it, of course, for me was that my sister was also there. But despite how hot it was, and how much confusion there was in the span of a few hours, it was actually an entertaining experience: we got to drive through suburban Connecticut, as well as the wooded areas, and see parts of another state, one very different from the New York I had just somewhat adjusted to. In the end, I&#39;m actually really happy we unexpectedly stopped in the wrong city because we got to experience a beautiful part of a new state.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/2016/08/09/stranded.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/2016/08/09/stranded.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deep in Thought</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt; 
&lt;br /&gt;
Whenever I get into our pool to go for a swim, I always end up thinking about and reflecting on my past and future. I&#39;m not really sure why - to be honest, I think being outside has a cathartic effect on me - I know I definitely need to go outside and be more active outside more often, but whenever I do go outside, I feel its positive effects immediately. And I&#39;ve reflected over a lot lately - most recently, about some of my fears. One fear I&#39;ve always had is looking at the deep end of a pool. It&#39;s just something that has scared me ever since I was a little girl, and it still sometimes scares me. But when I told my Dad, he suggested to look directly at the deep side in order to get over my fear. It&#39;s something I&#39;m slowly working on and hope to get over soon, because as I realized earlier this summer, there are things much more important than fears like these, ones that we can work towards getting over. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

While swimming, I began to think of the parallels of something as simple as looking directly at the deep end of a pool to bigger fears, ones we can&#39;t control. And what I realized is that there are some things that you have to just do in order to get over them, especially the more tangible things. Yet some fears, ones that are related to emotions, are not as simple to have a clear-cut solution for. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

For example, I was worried about the types of people I would meet in college, in fact, I was scared. Some of my closest friends are from high school, but a lot of my peers in high school were focused on only their grades, and forming cliques - and as a result, it was harder to connect with them because it felt as though they weren&#39;t focused on making new friends. I was scared the same would happen at Cal, but I am SO thankful that I have met people who share a similar mindset to me, and who I can confidently call great friends. The only thing I could do when coming to college was to be myself and hope to meet other unique people who were just being themselves as well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

I didn&#39;t want to get too deep, but since I was swimming in the deep end of the pool ... (that was super cheesy -- sorry!)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/2016/08/03/Deep-in-Thought.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/2016/08/03/Deep-in-Thought.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I scream for ice-cream</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt; 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
As I was looking through my photos to decide on my next post, I realized I had visited a ton of ice cream places. What I didn&#39;t realize was how many strong opinions I had formed on each place. Ice cream is the best thing ever, and I&#39;ve cultivated a list of the places I tried and which one tops the list. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/amplehills.JPG&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:500px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt;
(1) Best. Ice Cream. Ever. I did not &lt;i&gt;Yelp&lt;/i&gt; Ample Hills, nor did I know it even existed. I was on my way to the High Line, and as I was walking through the Meatpacking District, I saw Ample Hills was very busy. I didn&#39;t think much of it and continued to walk towards the High Line. But it was hot. Really hot. So as I walked down the High Line, and through Chelsea Market, I kept my eyes open for another appealing ice cream place, but nothing stood out to me like Ample Hills. So, of course, I decided to wait and try it on my way back home. I&#39;m so glad I made the decision - I&#39;ve never had such good strawberry ice cream. In my life. It literally had fresh strawberries in it, and though I chose the less healthy route, I felt like I was eating real strawberries. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/iceandvice.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ice and Vice&quot; style=&quot;width:500px;height:300px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt;
(2) Carded for Ice Cream. Ice and Vice was pretty good. Actually, it was really good, but it just didn&#39;t stand out or taste out of the ordinary. I, did, however, like it because of its unique flavors. I wanted to try the &lt;i&gt;Coffee and Champagne&lt;/i&gt; flavor, but the employees needed to see ID (isn&#39;t that so funny?). Since I&#39;m such a huge rebel, I asked my sister to get the flavor for me (shh...don&#39;t tell anyone) in a plain vanilla cone. It was delicious. My sister, on the other hand, got the Black Tea, &lt;i&gt;Lemon Charcoal Flavor&lt;/i&gt; in a &lt;i&gt;Moscow Mule&lt;/i&gt; cone. And my sister&#39;s friend got a scoop of &lt;i&gt; Hot Cheeto Ramen &lt;/i&gt; and a scoop of &lt;i&gt;Lobster Crouton ice cream &lt;/i&gt; in a blue corn and honey cone. By far the most interesting flavor, but I was, to be honest, a little scared to try those flavors. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/rename.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;More Ice Cream&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:500px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt;
(3) Vegan. Van Leeuwen Artisan Ice Cream was my least favorite shop. I&#39;ve started liking Mint Chocolate Chip, and my sister and I decided to split the &lt;i&gt; Vegan Milk Chocolate Chip &lt;/i&gt; flavor that day. I think it was a cool experience to try vegan ice cream, but I wasn&#39;t a huge fan of that particular ice cream. My experience with ice cream in general in NYC told me that New Yorkers love exoctic ice cream. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/chobani.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Chobani&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:500px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt;
(*Bonus*) This doesn&#39;t count as ice cream, but one day we were in SoHo and stopped at the Chobani store for a snack. My family loves greek yogurt, and my sister and I sort of freaked out that there was a store that served greek yogurt like an ice cream shop. We literally got to order a cup of yogurt with whatever toppings we wanted - I got the option with raspberries, granola, and honey, while my sister got the one with blueberries, walnuts, agave nectar, and chia, pumpkin, and sunflower seeds. Stopping at the Chobani store was so cool and different from anything I&#39;ve ever seen in California. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/2016/07/20/i-scream-for-ice-cream.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/2016/07/20/i-scream-for-ice-cream.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Visiting the MoMa</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/MoMa.JPG&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:500px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt; 

I visited a couple different museums in NYC, but the MoMa, unexpectedly, turned out to be my favorite. Yet I&#39;ve never liked museums. No matter how much energy I have before, nor how full I am, as soon as I enter any museum, I start to yawn and complain about how hungry I am. &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;But guess what? I surprised myself. I didn&#39;t even think (at least mostly) about being hungry. I definitely didn&#39;t think about sleep. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Fascinated by the impressionist art, I continued to walk through the gallery, admiring lesser known van Gogh paintings. I completely forgot that the &lt;b&gt;original&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;Starry Night&lt;/i&gt; is in the NYC MoMa. I&#39;m actually almost glad I did - I was completely in awe of the painting. Seeing something in real life, versus in pictures and books, is an entirely different experience. Below is one of my other favorite van Gogh paintings (&lt;i&gt;Olive Trees&lt;/i&gt;): &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/vangogh.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;van Gogh&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:500px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph-center&quot;&gt;It was also really amazing to get to see artwork by artists that I learned about in my French class:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/chagall.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Marc Chagall&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:500px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph-center&quot;&gt;Marc Chagall&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/degas.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;degas&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:500px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph-center&quot;&gt;Edgar Degas&#39; paintings had so much texture and depth, and I loved the fact that he used dancers to emulate Parisian life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph-center&quot;&gt;I also got to see work by Andy Warhol:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/warhol.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;warhol&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:500px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph-center&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Gold Marilyn Monroe&lt;/i&gt; -- Warhol used an actual piece of film tape to capture this image of Marilyn Monroe. His work is absolutely inspiring.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/2016/07/12/visiting-the-moma.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/2016/07/12/visiting-the-moma.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vegetarian Bean Burgers Recipe</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/Burger.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Vegetarian Burger&quot; style=&quot;width:300px;height:400px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt; 
&lt;b&gt;Servings: 4 &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

1 1/2 red onion&lt;br /&gt;
1/3 cup frozen peas&lt;br /&gt;
1/3 cup frozen corn&lt;br /&gt;
1 green pepper&lt;br /&gt;
2 peeled carrot sticks&lt;br /&gt;
1 jalapeno&lt;br /&gt;
1 clove garlic&lt;br /&gt;
1 can black beans&lt;br /&gt;
1/2 cup bread crumbs&lt;br /&gt;
1 tomato&lt;br /&gt;
1 Handful of salad leaves&lt;br /&gt;
4 whole wheat burger buns&lt;br /&gt;
1/3 cup hummus&lt;br /&gt;
Salt, cayenne to taste&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Recipe:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
To begin with, dice one red onion and mince the clove of garlic. Chop the green pepper, carrots, and jalapeno as well, and drain, rinse, and dry the can of black beans.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Pour two tablespoons of olive oil into a pan, and cook the diced red onion and minced garlic on medium heat for a couple of minutes. Once browned, add the peas, corn, pepper, and jalapeno, stir the vegetables and add salt and cayenne pepper to taste. Add another tablespoon of olive oil, and let the veggies cook for a few minutes on medium heat. Then, add the entire can of beans and let the beans and veggies cook for another two minutes. Remove the pan from heat and mix in the bread crumbs. Mash the entire mixture so that the beans create a paste and are not whole. At this time, if the mixture is falling apart, add more bread crumbs until you can create four balls out of the bean mixture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Once the bean and veggie mixture is ready, seperate it into four sections and create four patties with your hands. Grill the four patties on medium heat until both sides of the patty are brown. Once one side is completely grilled and the other side is not, place a slice of cheese on the finished side and allow the patty to finish grilling. Also grill the burger buns.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 

Once the patties and buns are done, spread hummus on all of the burger bun tops and place the salad leaves on the bottom of the buns. Then, slice the tomato and half onion to top the patties. 
 &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/2016/07/09/vegetarian-bean-burgers-recipe.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/2016/07/09/vegetarian-bean-burgers-recipe.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/Picnic.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Picnic Picture&quot; style=&quot;width:400px;height:400px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;paragraph&quot;&gt; 
This blog has been in the works for a few weeks now, and I&#39;m so excited to finally share it with all of you! The last six weeks have been a really fun time for me - I was in the heart of New York City, exploring, eating (hence the frequent recipes/food reviews you will see on this blog), and learning. This first post is a little more general, but over the next few posts, I&#39;m going to share with you some of my favorite adventures/discoveries :) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

This is a picture of a picnic that my sister and I packed. That Sunday, we actually went on a lot of mini adventures - before going to Central Park for our picnic, we took the subway to a famous grocery store, Zabar, known for its eight years of existence and specialty groceries. After our picnic (and a little nap), we visited a cafe, Cafe Lalo, famed for being featured in &quot;You&#39;ve Got Mail.&quot; We, of course, went back home and watched the movie (turns out Zabar was also featured in the movie!). Overall, it was a fun day, and I&#39;m excited to share some other stories with you all over the course of the next few weeks! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

My trip to NYC was, more than a trip, a learning experience. I learned so many things that I&#39;ve never had to before - how to use public transportation every day (something we in the Bay Area don&#39;t have to really worry about), become more responsible, and go out of my comfort zone - there were some days that I was hesitant to go places because I was afraid I would get lost in such an ovewhelming city. But I also realized it was a unique opportunity for me. I&#39;ve never really liked museums, but NYC has SO many unique museums and exhibitions that I now love them. I got to see some of my favorite artists, something I wouldn&#39;t have gotten the chance to do otherwise. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

I&#39;m going to share more detailed stories with you from my trip, so come back in a few days! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Love, &lt;br /&gt;
Avanti

&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 20:18:37 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/2016/07/07/welcome.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/2016/07/07/welcome.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
